question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Niko Bellic is the protagonist of Grand Theft Auto IV.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "Gosho Aoyama Made This Series: (Detective Conan \/ Case Closed!)", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "There is an island in Japan called \u014ckunoshima, A.K.A. &quot;Rabbit Island&quot;, so named because of it&#039;s huge population of rabbits.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "The title of the 1969 film &quot;Krakatoa, East_of Java&quot; is incorrect, as Krakatoa is in fact west of Java.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "There aren&#039;t any live-action clones in &quot;Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "Hungary is the only country in the world beginning with H.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "History",
                                      "question": "The first televised presidential debate was between Jimmy Carter and Gerald Ford.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The Sun rises from the North.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Scatman John&#039;s real name was John Paul Larkin.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Art",
                                       "question": "Venus of Willendorf is one of the earliest works of art, depicting the planets Mars and Venus embrace in the heavens at night.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
